<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BAJ Productions</title><link>http://bajproducations.com/</link><description>Recent content on BAJ Productions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://bajproducations.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>http://bajproducations.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bajproducations.com/about/</guid><description>The mission of BAJ Productions LLC is to create quality entertainment, which the whole family can enjoy. BAJ Productions founder, Barbara Albers Jackson has produced five shorts, three promos, written fourteen feature screenplays, two TV pilots, a stage play and published a graphic novel.
Notable among the shorts are Heavenly which received a Bronze Award at WorldFest Houston International Film Festival and Forgotten Son which received the Best Educational Short Award at the International Family Film Festival.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>http://bajproducations.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bajproducations.com/contact/</guid><description> Please email bajproductions@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Movie Projects</title><link>http://bajproducations.com/movie-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bajproducations.com/movie-projects/</guid><description>Movie Projects and Promos &amp;nbsp; Colors of My Mind Experimental Drama - 13 minute short
A boy's emotional state is depicted in colors as he learns his Dad is not his father.
Colors of My Mind Music Video
The Music Video from the Movie Colors Of My Mind Sung by Marcus.
Forgotten Son Drama - 10 minute short
Methamphetamine addiction as seen from the POV of a boy, whose mother is an addict.</description></item><item><title>Scripts</title><link>http://bajproducations.com/scripts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://bajproducations.com/scripts/</guid><description>Available scripts from award winning script writerBarbara Albers Jackson Scripts
TitleGenre Ability and JudgmentDrama Bird BrainComedy Cat HouseDramedy Deadly AmanitaRomantic Comedy / Murder Mystery Destruction By DesignAction/Fantasy/Comedy Fasten Your SeatbeltComedy Ivory TowersDrama KateRomantic Comedy The Marriage ContractRomantic Comedy Mel's BabyRomantic Comedy Miracles in MississippiTV Docudrama Mother is a VerbDrama Short RamaAnimation Timeless BaggageNew Age Romance Weekend DadFamily Stage Play Award:
Spirit of Moondance Award - Moondance Film Festival - THE MARRIAGE CONTRACT</description></item></channel></rss>